

Focused and diligent engineer with more than 11 years of experience. Experienced in BI development, SQL programming and large database analysis. Passionate about technology, data, and complex problem-solving. Highly organized and motivated, a fast learner with solid technical understanding and good communication skills.

Professional Experience

2021- now

Senior CSE & BI Developer, Mobideo(Saas, B2B)

- Building BI reports and dashboards to support variety of customers' use cases, using Spotfire Tibco
- Defining the data model and specifications for the reports based on users needs and environment setup
- Writing advanced SQL queries to extract and transform data from the data wharehouse
- Reconciling data, validating it, and handling errors on SQL Server
- Conducting data analysis of customers issues, requests, product use, and behavior
- Serving as the primary technical contact for ramping new customers, responsible for environment setup and deployment
- Managing the company's strategic accounts. Being the focal point for any technical matter
- Working closely with the Customer Success Managers, Program Managers, and Engineering to support customer needs and analyze product-level changes

2016-2020

Automation Engineer and Operations Analyst, Pelephone (Finance department)

- SQL developer, working with large scale Oracle DB (production environment)
- Conducting data analysis of financial and operational processes
- Providing data-driven solutions to support financial department needs
- Writing automation of processes, controls, and monitoring systems using Shell, Python and PL\SQL.
- Operating finance recurring processes and providing ad-hoc support to the business units
- Monitoring and troubleshooting the ongoing processes, on logic and technical level
- Automation programmer of Accounts Receivable (AR) systems
- Working with multiple stakeholders from R&D and various business units

2013-2016

Support and Automation Engineer, Hot Mobile

- Ongoing work with Oracle database and writing SQL queries to analyze and improve operational processes (production environment)
- Developing automated solutions that retired manual activity overhead for the operation teams
- Working directly with the information systems unit, business stakeholders in formulating technical requirements and business analysis to solve business problems
- Providing support on Comverse ONE system (CRM), understanding key processes and translate those into automated processes

2012-2013

3rd tier Support Specialist, Comverse Israel - Hot Mobile Project

- Member of the Ordering team on the Hot Mobile site. Providing technical support on Comverse ONE system (CRM) and serve as customer contact for ordering-related issues
- Creating, optimizing, and maintaining SQL queries that support application functionality and operation
- Since Feb 2013 Member of the Billing and Rating team
 - o Running all the billing cycles (Live and proforma), analyzing results & troubleshooting
 - Managing and handling all the suppress big and VIP accounts in the customer system

Skills

- Technical skills: SQL Server, Oracle Database, BigQuery, Spotfire, Tableau, Data Studio, Power BI, Python, HTML, Java, IIS, Kibana, Amazon s3, Octopus, Prisma, HubSpot, SysAid, TP, Shell script, UNIX, Confluence
- o Fluent in English and Hebrew

Education

B.Sc. Industrial Engineering and Management, The Open University